<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<information>
	
	<appname>Taekwindow</appname>
	<majorversion>0</majorversion>
	<minorversion>2</minorversion>
	<microversion>1</microversion>
	<build>0</build>
	<author>Thomas ten Cate</author>
	<email>ttencate+taekwindow@gmail.com</email>
	<website>http://taekwindow.sf.net/</website>
	<copyright>Copyright © 2006-2008, Thomas ten Cate</copyright>
	
	<description>
		Taekwindow is a simple, lightweight and free program that allows you to
		manipulate floating windows in Microsoft Windows in a way similar to
		many X11 window managers.
	</description>
	<installation>
		<ol>
			<li>
				You need to have the Microsoft .NET Framework, version 2.0 or later,
				installed to use the configuration tool. You can get the latest version
				of the framework from the <a href="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/en-us/netframework/aa569263.aspx">Microsoft website</a>.
			</li>
			<li>
				To install Taekwindow, simply extract the archive to any place you like.
				Make sure that the files are all in the same directory.
			</li>
			<li>
				Run <code>taekwindowconfig.exe</code> to configure the Taekwindow. The configuration
				tool can create a shortcut in the Startup section of your Start Menu, so
				Taekwindow is started when you log on to your computer.
			</li>
			<li>
				Optional: create a shortcut to taekwindowconfig.exe in your Start Menu.
			</li>
		</ol>
	</installation>
	<usage>
		<p>
			Start taekwindow.exe to load the program. Nothing will seem to happen,
			but you can now do the following:
		</p>
		<ul>
			<li>Hold left Alt and drag a window with the left mouse button to move it.</li>
			<li>Hold left Alt and drag a window with the right mouse button to resize it.</li>
		</ul>
		<p>
			(These buttons are configurable through the configuration tool.)
		</p>

		<p>
			To stop the program, just run <code>taekwindow.exe</code> again. It will not load
			itself, but rather stop the running instance and then quit. You can also
			stop it through the Task Manager if you prefer.
		</p>
	</usage>
	<configuration>
		<p>
			You can configure the program using the supplied configuration tool,
			<code>taekwindowconfig.exe</code>. Its usage should be self-explanatory.
		</p>

		<p>
			If the tool refuses to start, make sure that the .NET framework is
			installed. See Installation, above, for details.
		</p>
	</configuration>
	<bugs>

		<p>
			Please see the <a href="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?group_id=185457&amp;atid=913353">Bugs Tracker</a> at SourceForge.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can view the list of bugs in the current release as well as submit
			any new bugs you've discovered.
		</p>
	</bugs>
	<feature-requests>
		<p>
			Please see the <a href="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?group_id=185457&amp;atid=913356">Feature Requests Tracker</a>.
		</p>
		<p>
			Apart from a list of planned features, this also contains all feature
			requests submitted by users. You can of course submit your own.
		</p>
	</feature-requests>
	<versions>
		<version nr="0.2.1">
			<bugfix see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1653063&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913353">
				moving and resizing now works properly when dragging title bar or borders
			</bugfix>
			<bugfix see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1629393&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913353">
				moving and resizing now works on MDI child windows, instead of the parent
			</bugfix>
			<bugfix see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1894902&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913353">
				Taekwindow should no longer occasionally behave as if Alt is pressed when it is not
			</bugfix>
		</version>
		<version nr="0.2">
			<feature see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1629762&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913356">
				added a configuration tool
			</feature>
			<feature see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1653698&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913356">
				made the modifier and mouse buttons, as well as closest-corner resizing,
				into options
			</feature>
			<feature>
				added an option to the configuration tool for creating/deleting a Startup
				shortcut in the Start Menu
			</feature>
			<bugfix see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1682619&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913353">
				The error message “This application has failed to start because the applicaation
				configuration is incorrect. Reinstalling the application may fix this
				problem.” no longer appears.
			</bugfix>
		</version>
		<version nr="0.1.1">
			<feature see="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1632182&amp;group_id=185457&amp;atid=913356">
				implemented closest-corner resizing
			</feature>
		</version>
		<version nr="0.1">
			<feature>moving with Alt+left button, resizing from the bottom right corner with Alt+right button</feature>
		</version>
	</versions>
	<contact>
		Taekwindow is written by Thomas ten Cate. The preferred way to contact
		the author is through the <a href="http://taekwindow.sf.net/">Taekwindow web page</a>.
	</contact>
	<thanks>
		<p>I would like to thank the following people for their contributions to this project:</p>
		<thanklist>
			<thank who="Eamon Nerbonne and Mark IJbema">
				tested early versions of the program and provided valuable comments and suggestions.
			</thank>
			<thank who="Sylvain Vignaud">
				provided a patch to blacklist certain applications that require Alt-dragging in their normal mode of operation.
			</thank>
		</thanklist>
	</thanks>
	<license>
		<p>Copyright (c) 2006-2008, Thomas ten Cate.</p>
		<p>All rights reserved.</p>
		<p>
			Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
			modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
			met:
		</p>
		<ul>
			<li>
				Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
				this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
			</li>
			<li>
				Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
				notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
				documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
			</li>
		</ul>
		<p>
			THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
			"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
			LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A
			PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER
			OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
			EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
			PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR
			PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
			LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
			NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
			SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
		</p>
	</license>
	
</information>