<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<faq>

	<category id="general">
		
		<title>General</title>

		<qa id="name">
			<question>Why is it called Taekwindow?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>Taekwindow is a contraction of <em>taekwondo</em> (<a href="http://www.wtf.org/">WTF?</a>) and <em>window</em>. You are free to interpret this in any way you like, but the bottom line is that I just happen to like bad puns.</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

		<qa id="logo">
			<question>Why the logo?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>The red and blue circle is called the <em>Taeguk</em>. It is the national symbol of Korea, best known from the Korean national flag. The blue part symbolizes the water around the land. Combined with the mouse cursor, whose origin is obvious, I think it makes a nice logo.</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

		<qa id="license">
			<question>How is Taekwindow licensed?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>Taekwindow uses the BSD license. This is a very liberal license; in particular, you are free to distribute and modify the program. (Some websites got it wrong, and list Taekwindow under the GPL license instead.)</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

	</category>

	<category id="technical">

		<title>Technical</title>

		<qa id="vista">
			<question>Does it run on Windows Vista and Windows 7?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>As of version 0.3, these operating systems are fully supported. (Previous versions work reasonably as well.)</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

		<qa id="bit64">
			<question>Does it run on 64-bits Windows?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>As of version 0.3, it does.</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

		<qa id="dotnet">
			<question>Do I need the .NET framework?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>Version 0.2.x required the .NET framework for the configuration tool. As of version 0.3, .NET is no longer needed.</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

		<qa id="mac">
			<question>Will there be a Mac version?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>No. I don't own or use a Mac. Furthermore, Taekwindow is so closely tied to the Windows platform that porting it would come down to a complete rewrite.</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>
		
	</category>

	<category id="use">

		<title>Use</title>

		<qa id="iconhidden">
			<question>I hid the icon; how do I get it back?</question>
			<answer>
				<p>Just run <tt>taekwindow.exe</tt> again. The Preferences dialog will pop up, where you can re-enable the icon or quit the program.</p>
			</answer>
		</qa>

	</category>

</faq>